<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Seera Application</string>
    <string name="image">Image</string>
    <string name="teskilat">Teskilat</string>
    <string name="rating">Rating</string>

    <string name="cusur">Cesur returns to his father\'s village with an elaborate plan to avenge the death of his father. The only thing he hadn\'t planned for is Suhan, the daughter of the man he believes is responsible for his father\'s murder.</string>
    <string name="Aşk_Bu_Mu">Umut has been a thief since he was a kid. He constantly seeks the opportunity of his life and his family. He can\'t find either. Gülüm is a young girl who has no problems in her life, who has completed her schooling on time and is only a step away from her dreams. But before she takes that step towards her dreams, she hangs and falls. It is understood that Gülüm has liver failure. She\'ll die if she doesn\'t have a liver transplant. The fate of Umut and Gülüm merge at this point. Umut found the opportunity he had waited for the rest of his life. But this opportunity drags Umut into very difficult situations, and finds itself in a position that risks the lives of all loved ones. For Umut to come out of this vortex, he has to make very serious decisions. And love is worth everything? Is this love?</string>
    <string name="ariza">Ali Riza is a taxi driver preparing to marry his sister Nihan off to his dear friend; Halide Gurkan attends Fuat Ersoylu\'s magnificent party given on the occasion of his father\'s birthday and during the party Fuat\'s son Burak proposes to Halide, who refuses, then leaves the party and gets into Ali Riza\'s taxi. Burak follows Halide and forces her out of Ali Riza\'s taxi; Ali Riza intervenes, a fight breaks out, and Burak takes the first shameful slap of his life from Ali Riza. Burak does not forget about this, so later he invades Ali Riza\'s sister\'s wedding, but things get out of control and Burak happens to shoot and kill Ali Riza\'s sister Nihan. How will Ali Riza avenge his sister\'s murder?</string>
    <string name="soz">Yavuz Karasu, a well-trained Turkish soldier, is in Istanbul with his fiance where a terrorist operation takes place. Dr. Bahar, who is not a surgeon, tries to save his fiance. After this incident, Yavuz goes back to Karabayir and Bahar follows him all the way to give him something that belongs to him. Another incident happens and he is chosen to be the commander of a team whose mission is to catch a terrorist and protect Karabiyir and their country Turkey. The whole team is solid, consistent, and willing to sacrifice their lives for the sake of their country.</string>
    <string name="sever">Aşk Tesadüfleri Sever, yönetmenliğini Ömer Faruk Sorak\'ın yaptığı 2010 Türk aşk filmidir. Film 4 Şubat 2011 tarihinde gösterime girmiştir. Filmin soundtrack albümü de filmin yayınlandığı tarihte yayınlanmıştır. Çocukluk ve ilk gençlik yılları boyunca yolları Ankara’da kesişen ve 2010 yılında İstanbul\’da tanışan Özgür (Mehmet Günsür) ve Deniz (Belçim Bilgin), kendilerini engellerle dolu aşk macerasının içinde bulurlar. Bir yandan da geri dönüşlerle onların geçmişlerini izlerken, diğer yandan da Türkiye\’nin 70\'li, 80\'li, 90\'lı ve 2000\'li yıllarında gezerek, dönemin unutulmaya yüz tutmuş popüler kültür öğeleri, müzikleri, yaşam biçimleri Aşk Tesadüfleri Sever’in nostaljik yönünü tamamlıyor.</string>
    <string name="Teskilat_para">The series of the Teşkilat deals with the story of seven lovers of the motherland who went \“underground\”, accepting a task for their country in which they had to give up their own lives and become invisible in the crowd. A terrorist attack is planned on the SIHA factory in Ankara. It is established that the attack was organized by foreign intelligence services. After that, a secret team is established within the National Intelligence Agency. The purpose of this team is to identify and eliminate the forces behind the attack.</string>
   <string name="marasli"> Marasli (BurakDeniz) is a retired soldier turned bookstore owner. For Marasli, life changed drastically after his daughter is shot. One day, the beautiful Mahur (AlinaBoz) enters Marasli\'s bookstore and on that same day, she involuntarily gets involved in an incident. Marasli saves Mahur\'s life and from that day onwards, their fates will be linked.</string>-->



    <string name="carpisma">It is about life that intersects with the collision of four cars.Çarpışma is a Turkish action drama television series starring Kıvanç Tatlıtuğ, Elçin Sangu, Onur Saylak, Melisa Aslı Pamuk and Alperen Duymaz. It premiered on Show TV on November 22, 2018 and concluded on May 30, 2019. </string>
    <string name="Kiralık">When Defne\'s brother gets into debt and is held captive, Defne is forced to accept an offer in exchange for the money. She has to make omer, a wealthy shoe designer who owns a company, fall in love with her and marry her.</string>
    <string name="cukur">A dangerous neighborhood, "The Pit", ran by a noble mafia family called Koçovali. When the family is in the danger of losing the control of The Pit, their youngest son now must come back to his home, where he could never escape from.</string>
    <string name="Kendime">An introvert romancer delves into a reality check after he finds out that he was risen to the bait by his deceased former lover. He breaks up with his girlfriend and starts searching for answers.</string>
    <string name="unutursam">An old pop singer who has Alzheimer\'s returns to her old house where she remembers her old days of climbing the stairs of fame and fortune while trying to deal with her older sister who holds her responsible for her ruined life.</string>
    <string name="Issız">A young children\'s costume designer named Ada falls in love with a cook named Alper, but modern life, Alper\'s way of life, threatens to keep them apart.</string>
    <string name="icerde">İçerde is a Turkish action thriller television series produced by Ay Yapım. The series first aired on 19 September 2016 on Show TV. The series received mixed reviews throughout its original run, however the performances of both lead actors Çağatay Ulusoy and Aras Bulut İynemli were met with critical acclaim.</string>
    <string name="Delibal">Delibal is a 2015 Turkish film directed by Ali Bilgin. Çağatay Ulusoy and Leyla Lydia Tuğutlu starred in the film. The film was released on 25 December 2015.</string>
    <string name="biküçük">A Small September Affair is a 2014 Turkish drama film directed by Kerem Deren and starring Engin Akyürek and Farah Zeynep Abdullah.</string>
    <string name="Ikimizin">In a small town, a young girl called Çiçek falls in love with Do?an, a literature teacher who has just arrived in town. Although Do?an tries to fight this forbidden love, he can\'t stay away from Çiçek.</string>
    <string name="Kelebeğin">Two young poets suffering from tuberculosis try to survive the famine-stricken times of World War II. When they both fall in love with the same girl, they compete for her affections with their poetry.</string>
    <string name="ramo">Ramo is a Turkish crime drama and action television series written by Yılmaz Şahin and directed by Yağız Alp Akaydın, starring Murat Yıldırım in the titular role. This show is about a feud between two families and a love story between Ramo and Si̇bel. It was filmed in Adana, Turkey and premiered on 14 January 2020.</string>
    <string name="bahat">Ada grew up among women who believe they will be happy marrying the first men with whom they fall in love. But when her love interest Rüzgar abandons her, a challenging, romantic journey between love and destiny awaits her.</string>
    <string name="leorm_ipsom">Leorm ipsom</string>
    <string name="movie_name">Movie Name</string>
    <string name="popular">Popular</string>
    <string name="top_rated">Top Rated</string>
    <string name="revenue">Revenue</string>

</resources>